question_data = [
 {"type": "boolean",
  "difficulty": "hard",
  "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
  "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
  "correct_answer": "True",
  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
  "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
  "question": "&quot;Kamea,&quot; the Gilbertese Islander word for dog, is derived from the English phrase &quot;Come here!&quot;",
  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
  "question": "In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.",
  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
  "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True",
  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                    "question": "&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.",
                                    "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Art",
  "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.", "correct_answer": "False",
  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Mathematics",
                                   "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False",
                                   "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
  "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
  "question": "The United States of America was the first country to launch a man into space.",
  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
